http://www.wabusinessnews.com.au/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Business News takes the privacy of its users and subscribers seriously. We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our users while providing a personalised and valuable service. This Privacy Policy Statement explains the data processing practices of Business News. If you have any requests concerning your personal information, wish to make any amendment to your personal information or have any queries with regard to these practices please contact us by e-mail at privacy@businessnews.com.au.Information collectedPersonal information is collected by Business News. We collect personal information from you through the use of enquiry and registration forms and every time you e-mail us your detailsWe also collect information automatically about your visit to our site. The information obtained in this way, which includes demographic data and browsing patterns, is only used in aggregate form.Use of personal informationWe process personal information collected via the site for the purposes of:providing a personalised serviceconducting market research surveysrunning competitionsproviding you with information about products and services offered by Business News.We may disclose your information to business partners and third party suppliers we engage to provide services which may involve processing data on our behalf. We also use information in aggregate form:to build up marketing profilesto aid strategic developmentto manage our relationship with advertisers and to audit usage of the siteUse of cookiesWe use "cookies" to identify you when you visit the site and to build up a demographic profile.A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information back from the browser.Our use of cookies also allows registered users to be presented with a personalised version of the site.Website Analytics & Google AdWordsBusinessnews.com.au utilises Google Analytics to track user engagement and allow for remarketing services via Google AdWords.The Google AdWords remarketing service is used to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network.Our site and our mobile application use first party cookies and third-party cookies, to, among other things, analyse and track users' use of the site and our mobile application, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand online activity. By accessing the site and our mobile application, you consent to the collection and use of your information. Any data collected will be used in accordance with both our own and Google’s privacy policy.You may set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page;opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page; and/orManage your browser cookie settings.We do not transfer personal information to third-party vendors.Internet-based transfersGiven that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing our website and communicating electronically with us you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way.
STANDING BY BUSINESS. TRUSTED BY BUSINESS.Subscription Options
What is Data & Insights?
